{
  "title": "韓国語単語①",
  "data": [
    {"question": "가게", "answer": ["店"]},
  {"question": "가족", "answer": ["家族"]},
  {"question": "개", "answer": ["犬"] },
  {"question": "겨울", "answer": ["冬"]},
  {"question": "그림", "answer": ["絵"]},
  {"question": "길", "answer": ["道"]},
  {"question": "나라", "answer": ["国"]},
  {"question": "나이", "answer": ["年齢"]},
  {"question": "남편", "answer": ["夫"]},
  {"question": "내일", "answer": ["明日"]},
  {"question": "눈", "answer": ["目","雪"]},
  {"question": "다음주", "answer": ["来週"]},
  {"question": "닭", "answer": ["ニワトリ"]},
  {"question": "도서관", "answer": ["図書館"]},
  {"question": "동생", "answer": ["弟","妹"] },
  {"question": "마음", "answer": ["心"]},
  {"question": "매일", "answer": ["毎日"]},
  {"question": "먼저", "answer": ["まず"]},
  {"question": "몸", "answer": ["体"]},
  {"question": "문제", "answer": ["問題"]},
  {"question": "밑", "answer": ["下"]},
  {"question": "바지", "answer": ["ズボン"]},
  {"question": "밤", "answer": ["夜"]},
  {"question": "방", "answer": ["部屋"]},
  {"question": "병", "answer": ["病気"]},
  {"question": "봄", "answer": ["春"]},
  {"question": "비행기", "answer": ["飛行機"] },
  {"question": "사진", "answer": ["写真"]},
  {"question": "생일", "answer": ["誕生日"]},
  {"question": "선생님", "answer": ["先生"]},
  {"question": "가을", "answer": ["秋"] },
  {"question": "감기", "answer": ["風邪"] },
  {"question": "거의", "answer": ["ほとんど"]},
  {"question": "교사", "answer": ["教師"] },
  {"question": "기분", "answer": ["気分"] },
  {"question": "꽃", "answer": ["花"]},
  {"question": "나무", "answer": ["木"]},
  {"question": "날씨", "answer": ["天気"]},
  {"question": "낮", "answer": ["昼"] },
  {"question": "농구", "answer": ["バスケ"] },
  {"question": "다음", "answer": ["次"]},
  {"question": "단어", "answer": ["単語"]},
  {"question": "대학", "answer": ["大学"] },
  {"question": "돈", "answer": ["お金"] },
  {"question": "딸", "answer": ["娘"]},
  {"question": "맛", "answer": ["味"] },
  {"question": "머리", "answer": ["頭"]},
  {"question": "모두", "answer": ["みんな"] },
  {"question": "문", "answer": ["ドア"]},
  {"question": "물", "answer": ["水"]},
  {"question": "바다", "answer": ["海"] },
  {"question": "밖", "answer": ["外"]},
  {"question": "밥", "answer": ["ご飯"]},
  {"question": "배", "answer": ["お腹"]},
  {"question": "병원", "answer": ["病院"]},
  {"question": "머리", "answer": ["雨"]},
  {"question": "사과", "answer": ["りんご"] },
  {"question": "산", "answer": ["山"]},
  {"question": "선물", "answer": ["プレゼント"]},
  {"question": "설탕", "answer": ["砂糖"]},
  {"question": "소금", "answer": ["塩"] },
  {"question": "손", "answer": ["手"] },
  {"question": "술", "answer": ["お酒"]},
  {"question": "시계", "answer": ["時計"]},
  {"question": "식당", "answer": ["食堂"]},
  {"question": "아내", "answer": ["妻"]},
  {"question": "아이", "answer": ["子供"]},
  {"question": "안경", "answer": ["メガネ"]},
  {"question": "속", "answer": ["中"]},
  {"question": "수업", "answer": ["授業"]},
  {"question": "숫자", "answer": ["数字"] },
  {"question": "시장", "answer": ["市場"]},
  {"question": "신발", "answer": ["靴"] },
  {"question": "아들", "answer": ["息子"] },
  {"question": "아침", "answer": ["朝"] },
  {"question": "양쪽", "answer": ["両方"]},
  {"question": "가깝다", "answer": ["近い"]},
  {"question": "고프다", "answer": ["空腹"]},
  {"question": "나쁘다", "answer": ["悪い"]},
  {"question": "높다", "answer": ["高い"]},
  {"question": "덥다", "answer": ["暑い"]},
  {"question": "맞다", "answer": ["合う"]},
  {"question": "비싸다", "answer": ["高い"] },
  {"question": "싫다", "answer": ["嫌い"]},
  {"question": "아름답다", "answer": ["美しい"] },
  {"question": "어렵다", "answer": ["難しい"]},
  {"question": "같다", "answer": ["同じ"]},
  {"question": "길다", "answer": ["長い"] },
  {"question": "낮다", "answer": ["低い"]},
  {"question": "늦다", "answer": ["遅い"]},
  {"question": "맛없다", "answer": ["不味い"]},
  {"question": "멀다", "answer": ["遠い"] },
  {"question": "쉽다", "answer": ["簡単"]},
  {"question": "싸다", "answer": ["安い"] },
  {"question": "아프다", "answer": ["痛い"]},
  {"question": "밉다", "answer": ["憎い"] },
  {"question": "가다", "answer": ["行く"] },
  {"question": "걸다", "answer": ["かける"] },
  {"question": "기다리다", "answer": ["待つ"]},
  {"question": "나가다", "answer": ["出て行く"]},
  {"question": "내다", "answer": ["出す"]},
  {"question": "넣다", "answer": ["入れる"]},
  {"question": "놓다", "answer": ["置く"]},
  {"question": "닫다", "answer": ["閉める"]},
  {"question": "되다", "answer": ["〜になる"]},
  {"question": "들어가다", "answer": ["入って行く"]},
  {"question": "만나다", "answer": ["会う"] },
  {"question": "말하다", "answer": ["話す"]},
  {"question": "모르다", "answer": ["知らない"]},
  {"question": "믿다", "answer": ["信じる"]},
  {"question": "배우다", "answer": ["習う"]},
  {"question": "벗다", "answer": ["脱ぐ"]},
  {"question": "보다", "answer": ["見る"]},
  {"question": "서다", "answer": ["立つ"]},
  {"question": "시작되다", "answer": ["始まる"]},
  {"question": "쓰다", "answer": ["書く・使う・被る"]},
  {"question": "가르치다", "answer": ["教える"] },
  {"question": "계시다", "answer": ["いらっしゃる"] },
  {"question": "끝나다", "answer": ["終わる"]},
  {"question": "나다", "answer": ["出る"]},
  {"question": "다니다", "answer": ["通う"]},
  {"question": "돌아가다", "answer": ["帰る"]},
  {"question": "들다", "answer": ["持つ"]},
  {"question": "마시다", "answer": ["飲む"]},
  {"question": "만들다", "answer": ["作る"]},
  {"question": "먹다", "answer": ["食べる"]},
  {"question": "못하다", "answer": ["できない"]},
  {"question": "받다", "answer": ["受け取る"]},
  {"question": "버리다", "answer": ["捨てる"]},
  {"question": "보내다", "answer": ["送る"] },
  {"question": "살다", "answer": ["生きる"]  },
  {"question": "세다", "answer": ["数える"] },
  {"question": "신다", "answer": ["履く"] },
  {"question": "앉다", "answer": ["座る"]},
  {"question": "같이", "answer": ["一緒に"]}, 
  {"question": "다시", "answer": ["もう一度"]},
  {"question": "또", "answer": ["また"]},
  {"question": "빨리", "answer": ["速く"]},
  {"question": "언제나", "answer": ["いつも"]},
  {"question": "천천히", "answer": ["ゆっくり"]},
  {"question": "가만히", "answer": ["じっと"]},
  {"question": "갑자기", "answer": ["急に"]},
  {"question": "다", "answer": ["全部"]},
  {"question": "더", "answer": ["もっと"]},
  {"question": "많이", "answer": ["多く"]},
  {"question": "아주", "answer": ["とても"]},
  {"question": "좀", "answer": ["少し"]},
  {"question": "가끔", "answer": ["時々"]},
  {"question": "가장", "answer": ["最も"]},
  {"question": "겨우", "answer": ["やっと"]},
  {"question": "알다", "answer": ["知る"]},
  {"question": "오다", "answer": ["来る"]},
  {"question": "웃다", "answer": ["笑う"]},
  {"question": "이야기하다", "answer": ["話す"]},
  {"question": "입다", "answer": ["着る"] },
  {"question": "자다", "answer": ["寝る"]},
  {"question": "잡다", "answer": ["つかむ"]},
  {"question": "공부하다", "answer": ["勉強する"]},
  {"question": "생각하다", "answer": ["考える"]},
  {"question": "열다", "answer": ["開く"]},
  {"question": "울다", "answer": ["泣く"]},
  {"question": "일어나다", "answer": ["起きる"]},
  {"question": "읽다", "answer": ["読む"]},
  {"question": "잊다", "answer": ["忘れる"] },
  {"question": "잘하다", "answer": ["上手"]},
  {"question": "결혼하다", "answer": ["結婚する"] },
  {"question": "노래하다", "answer": ["歌う"]},
  {"question": "행복하다", "answer": ["幸せ"]}
  ]
}
